<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package Documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About CA Harvest 

================================
CA Harvest Software Change Manager is a software tool for the configuration management (revision control, SCM, etc.) of source code and other software development assets.

About Automic's CA Harvest Package
================================

Automate the usage of harvest commands through various actions. These actions are basic building blocks to achieve a specific business goal.
*Create Package
*Get Package
*Promote Package
*Demote Package
*Checkout Local 

=Supported Harvest versions=
* Harvest v12.6

=Limitations=
* No known limitations.

=Setup=
* Oracle JRE 1.7 or higher must be installed on Agent OS and "java" must be set as executable on the same.
* Actions must run on the same machine where the Harvest Client is installed.
* Verify that the CA_SCM_HOME Environment variable is set to Harvest Client Install directory

=Variables=
(none)

=Common Input=
-Broker*:           Specify the hostname of the Harvest Broker. E.g. vviehrv01
-Port*:               Specify the port number of the Harvest Broker. The default port is 5101. Port range is 1 to 65536.
-Username*:     Specify the username to connect to the Harvest Broker. E.g. harvest
-Password*:      Specify the password to connect to the Harvest Broker.

=Actions=
Following actions are supported for Harvest.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_PACKAGE
*  Action Description: This action creates a new change package in a given Harvest project.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.DEMOTE_PACKAGE
* Action Description: This action demotes the package to revert back my promoted package for the required change.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.PROMOTE_PACKAGE
* Action Description: This action promotes the mentioned change package(s) from the given from-state to to-state.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.CHECKOUT_LOCAL
* Action Description:  This action helps to get files from the repository to the local directory.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.GET_PACKAGE
* Action Description: This action gets the package details in a given Harvest project.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.GET_VERSION
* Action Description: This action retrieves the version details of a Harvest item.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.CHECKIN_LOCAL
* Action Description: This action helps to check in local file(s) to the Harvest repository.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.CHECKOUT_BY_AGENT
* Action Description:  This action checks out files from a Harvest repository to a host accessed by the specified agent.

* Action Name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.CHECKIN_BY_AGENT
* Action Description:  This action checks in file(s) to the Harvest repository using a specified file agent.

* Action Name:PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_HARVEST.PUB.ACTION.TAKE_SNAPSHOT 
* Action Description: This action takes a snapshot for a given project with the latest versions in the view.

]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>